我去催催你们的沙拉
I'll go check on your salads.
奥列格 为什么沙拉要这么久
Oleg, what's the hold up with the salads?
因为我压根就没做
I never made one before.
我最爱的两家伙 大格格跟桑秋
My two favorite guys, Big Doug and Sancho,
居然点了沙拉
are ordering salads?
平常点的BLT呢
What happened to their usual BLTs?
汉堡 千层面 玉米饼[BLT]
Burgers, lasagna, and tacos?
他们说他们在减肥
They said they want to lose weight.
而且无论点了什么
And no matter what you order,
在这里催吐总比家里容易嘛
it's easier to throw up here than at home.
真不懂为啥现在没人喜欢胖子了
I don't get why nobody wants to be fat anymore.
奥普拉胖时的那几季脱口秀最好看了
The fat seasons of Oprah were always the best.
你说得对耶
You're right.
她节目都是一年超好看一年不好看
Every other year of Oprah was the best years.
我听说两位面红小苹果想减肥呀
What is this I hear about you blushing beauties on a diet?
我们不是羞涩脸红
Oh, we're not blushing.
是坐下来运动量太大而脸红
We're just still flushed from sitting down.
而且我们想有个好体型
And we're trying to get in shape.
是啊 希望能有
Yeah, preferably a shape
不会让人想到葫芦的体型
that doesn't resemble a seasonal gourd.
而且我的女朋友也想我减肥
Plus my girlfriend wants me to slim down
旅行一起坐飞机时 她才能跟我坐同一排
so we can sit on the same side of the plane when we travel.
好吧 大格格
Well, Big Doug,
你告诉你家那位幸运姑娘 我就宁愿跟一个
you tell that lucky lady that I would rather date a man
胸比我大的男人交往
with boobs bigger than mine
也不跟自己带沙拉调料来餐厅的娘炮交往
than a man who brings his own salad dressing to a restaurant.
上派
Pie me.
樱桃派 南瓜派 还是椰浆派
Cherry, pumpkin, or coconut cream?
都要了
Yes.
麦克斯·布莱克
Max Black,
打从青春期就给无数男性脸上带来笑容
bringing smiles to men's faces since puberty.
我刚跟那桌的男的聊天了
I just talked to this guy at--
好像是三号桌吧 我到现在还没搞清桌号
I think it's table three, I still don't know the numbers.
总之 他问了"有啥新鲜的"
Anyway, he asked, "What's new?"
我就跟他说我们要开一家甜品吧
And I told him we were opening a dessert bar
明天在机场开幕
at the airport tomorrow.
然后我才发现他原来是要问我 这一周
Then I realized he was asking what kind of pot
我有啥新鲜的大麻卖
I was selling this week.
你为什么要跟别人说我们在机场工作的事
Why are you telling people about us and the airport?
就跟你到处跟人说你有HPV[性病]一样
It's like when you told everyone you thought you had HPV.
这算是州政府强制要求之类的吧
That was a state-mandated kind of thing.
哟 快看看是谁啊
Oh, look who it is--
在机场上班的"上等人"呢
the airport people.
两位姐是在办欢乐时光吗
You guys putting together a little happy hour?
是跟西南航空的小鲜肉一起乐呵
With the jocks at Southwest?
还是跟红人们去维珍航空航站乐呵啊
Or the "in crowd" at the Virgin Terminal?
你知道谁会因处男末期[航站]而死吗
You know who's going to be a terminal virgin?
我随便你怎么咒我威胁我
You can make all the death threats you want,
但你知道我是靠什么一直活着的吗
but you know what will keep me alive?
就靠着你俩在机场工作这事来吊着口气
The fact that you two work at the airport.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
待嫁新娘大驾光临
Here comes the almost bride.
你们看过比我更美的待嫁新娘吗
Did you ever see a prettier almost bride?
我是指出了珍妮佛·安妮斯顿之外的
I mean, you know, besides Jennifer Aniston.
苏菲 你下周就要结婚了
Sophie, it's only one week till the wedding,
这是你最后一次扑倒我的机会了
so this is your last chance to take a run at me.
保证不会让你失望哦
Now you won't be disappointed.
我还是床上一条龙
I'm still very sexually active
但五分钟后就是虫
for the first five minutes.
厄尔
Oh, Earl.
如果我真来扑你
If I took a run at you,
你绝对跟卡通人物一样破墙而逃
you'd go right through that wall like Wile E. Coyote.
伴娘们好啊
Hey, bridesmaid.
你好啊 苏菲
Hey, Sophie.
奥列格
Hey, Oleg.
你乌克兰的兄弟给你留了言
You got a message from your brother in the Ukraine.
约申科打来了吗
Yoshinko called?
来 你听听他的留言
Yeah, hear this message.
什么留言啊
What was the message?
"奥列格 你昨晚看《家有阿福》了吗"
"Hey, Oleg, did you see last night's Alf?"
不是啦 我不会说乌克兰语
Nah... I don't speak Ukrainian.
毕竟... 我是谁啊 皇后区的水管工吗
I mean, what am I, a plumber in Queens?
所以只好把整台答录机搬来了
No, so I brought the whole thing in.
听他说吧
Here he is.
奥列格
Oleg...
再见
Good-bye.
他说什么了
What did he say?
他不来了
He's not coming.
我听得懂一点
I understood a little
我家以前有个俄罗斯互惠生伴我长大
'cause I had a Russian au pair growing up.
但她把我好的牛仔裤漂白了以后就滚蛋了
You know, until she bleached my good jeans.
约申科不能来婚礼了
Yoshinko can't come to the wedding.
他上了禁飞名单 禁驾名单
He's on a no-fly list, a no-drive list,
还有禁走名单
and a no-walk list.
因为他坐牢了
He's in jail.
可是他不是要当你的伴郎吗
Oh, but he was gonna be your best man.
我还特别订了有他名字的火腿肉
I got a ham engraved for him.
别担心 宝贝 我会找到人
Don't worry, baby, I'll find someone.
谁都可以嘛
It could be anyone.
都不见得是伴郎 半良也行嘛
He doesn't even have to be the best or even good.
我得拉低标准
I'll have to lower my standards.
阿憨
Han,
你愿意当我的伴郎吗
will you be my best man?
你只说拉低 没说低到地下室啊
You said lower, not sub-basement.
奥列格 我得考虑考虑
Well, Oleg, I'll need to think about it.
我答应
Yes.
太好了 阿憨
Great. So Han,
那你来负责明天的单身汉派对
you're in charge of the bachelor party tomorrow.
我要一个能毁了所有参与者三观节操
I want a night that will disgrace all involved.
隔天吃早午餐时 大家再也无法
A night where no one can look each other in the eye
直视对方双眼的单身汉之夜
at brunch the next day.
阿憨
Wow, Han.
单身汉派对的责任很大啊
Bachelor party's a big responsibility.
你有认识任何成人可以进店里帮你买酒吗
Do you know any grown-ups who can buy you beer?
麦克斯 快点
Max, hurry.
这个粉色机场地牢的开幕
The grand opening of this pink airport dungeon
再过几分钟就要到了
is in a few minutes.
刚才运输安全局的队也排太久
That TSA line took forever.
还记得那个满身钢镚的女人吗
The woman with all those nickels?
上次看到身上这么多变化[硬币]的女人
I haven't seen that much change on a lady
还是查兹·波诺[变性人]呢
since Chaz Bono.
别担心
Don't worry,
我跟运输安全局的人交上朋友了
I'm making friends in the TSA.
朱迪 大胖妞 有小胡子
Judy, big gal, little beard?
中午跟她约了在马航旁边的
Having lunch with her at the Wok N' Roll
中餐馆吃午饭
near Malaysia Airlines.
那一带最近还挺清幽的
It's pretty quiet over there these days.
姑娘们
Hey, ladies.
开张日 我好兴奋啊
Opening day, I'm so excited
从我起床我奶头就兴奋硬到能射飞刀了
my nipples have been shooting daggers since I woke up.
我是认真的 我上一次这么兴奋
Seriously, I haven't been this excited
还是我爸妈把我送进军校的时候
since my parents sent me to military school.
天啊 为什么基佬就得啥事都这么欢乐呢
God, does everything have to be fun when you're gay?
如果不欢乐 那你一定是哪里"做"错了
If it isn't, you're not doing it right.
我只是很开心我可以待在店前
I'm just happy I get to be out front here.
我终于不用被塞后面了
Finally, I won't be stuffed in the back.
除非在男厕遇到共和党议员
I mean unless I run into a Republican senator
那我让他塞"后面"
in the men's room.
来吧 开门营业吧
Come on, let's open up.
这串钥匙要不要这么屌炸天
But dat key though?
我爱死这份工作了
I love this job.
等等 是不是应该谁来致辞几句
Wait, should someone make a speech?
还致辞咧
A speech?
如果你想听我对这里开张营业的想法
If you want to hear my thoughts on opening this place,
那我可以电邮抄送你我的自杀遗书
I'll just CC you on my suicide note.
好吧 我来说两句
Fine, I'll make a speech.
我想对对我说过这些话的学校清洁工说
To all the school janitors who told me I'd never have
你们说我不会有大串钥匙的一天
my own giant set of keys,
这塞不进任何口袋里
too big for any pocket,
还说我吻功很差
and that I wasn't a good kisser?
你们都去吃屎吧
They can all suck it.
起来吧 大门 起来吧
Yes! Rise, gate, rise!
干得好 大门
Ooh, you go, gate.
我在权力里醉了
Yes, I'm drunk with power.
也真有点小醉酒
Also, a little drunk.
好咧 客人要来啦
All right. Here they come.
是啊
Yep.
随时会来
Any minute.
我们这运气没话说
Just our luck.
撞上了机场唯一不繁忙的一天
The one day the airport isn't crowded.
看来够时间让我去男洗手间里
Well, I guess I have time to go check my make-up
补补妆
in the men's room.
是阿憨
It's Han.
他想要我们去参加今晚奥列格的单身汉派对
He wants us to come to Oleg's bachelor party tonight.
我以前也接过这种电话
I've gotten a call like this before,
但通常都是从含有"转流苏"服务的公司
but usually it's through a service that involves
打来给我去开工干活的邀约
making some tassels spin in opposite directions.
别想
No way.
你明知道我都安排好今晚回家大哭一场了
You know I was planning on going home and crying tonight.
这事阿憨办的派对呢
Han is planning a party.
去了必哭
You will cry there for sure.
这倒是真的 我现在在哪都能哭了
That's true. I really can cry anywhere now.
至少我赚了这项技能
I guess I've got that at least.
麦克斯 真不敢相信我在机场工作
I can't believe I work at the airport, Max.
我让你拿着我的大钥匙串 你会开心点吗
Hey, would you feel better if you held my giant keys?
你们好
Hello?
你好啊
Hello.
欢迎光临 我们的天字第一号客人
Welcome, you're our first customer.
有奖拿吗
Do I get a prize?
你是我的奖吗
Is it you?
我乐意了 我爱死这份工作了
I'm on board now. I love this job.
欢迎光临 各位
Welcome, everyone.
我是主持人 李憨
I'm your M.C., Han Lee,
今晚的疯狂派对就从几个
gonna get the crazy party started here
下流 猥亵的笑话开始
with some dirty, racy jokes.
这是我这辈子去过最死气沉沉的地方了
This is the deadest place I've ever been to,
而我有一次起床是在天堂醒来
and I once woke up in Heaven.
好的 笑话来啦
Okay, here we go.
请问魔方与鸡鸡的共同点在哪里
What do a Rubik's Cube and a penis have in common?
越玩越难[硬]
The more you play with it, the harder it gets.
魔方是80年代很受欢迎的玩具
A Rubik's Cube was a popular '80s toy.
你瞎爆了 下一个
You suck! Next act.
请问海象跟保鲜盒的共同点在哪里
What do a walrus and a Tupperware have in common?
稍等一下
Hold on a minute.
答案是跟密封[海豹]有关...
Something about a seal being tight...
我收到乔希的短信 那个机长
I just got a text from Josh, the pilot.
他说"在干嘛啊 小妞"
He says, "What's up, you?"
是不是很萌呀
Isn't that cute?
忘记你叫什么也萌吗
Cute that he forgot your name?
空虚寂寞冷得有点久了 是吧
It's really been a long time for you, hasn't it?
上周我脱内裤时 下面都鬼哭狼嚎了
I took off my underwear last week and a coyote howled.
观众太难搞
Tough crowd.
我指的就是你 麦克斯
I'm talking about you, Max.
加油啊 阿憨 放轻松点
Oh come on, Han. Loosen up.
喝杯酒
Have a drink.
有马丁尼 苹果马丁尼 任何一丁点的
A martini, an appletini, anything teeny.
就喝纯伏特加吧
Nah, just do a vodka shot.
盛酒的小杯子 在你手上看起来是正常大小
If nothing else, the glass will look normal-sized in your hand
好歹这能让我们笑一下
and I'll have a laugh.
反正死不了
Can't hurt.
真要被辣死
But it did.
谢谢你帮我办派对 阿憨
Thanks for the party, Han.
几点开始啊
What time is it starting?
我从来没当过伴郎[最好男人]
I've never been a best man.
这压力山大啊
It's a lot of pressure.
是啊 当男人的确对你太难
Yeah, being a man would be hard for you.
毕竟你从来没当过男人
You've never been one before.
更别说是最好的男人了
Let alone the best one.
这里面装了什么这么难入口 毛玻璃吗
What's in that, ground glass?
这派对[党]比某党还糟糕
Ugh, this party is worse than the communist party.
他们还杀了我一半的家人呢
And they killed half my family.
奥列格 别担心 我来让你的派对嗨起来
Oleg, don't worry, I'll get this party started.
我打电话给我以前的学校女同学就行
I'm making a call to some girls I went to school with.
校名是第七大道女婊学院
The Slut Academy on Seventh.
俗称"纽约大学"
Commonly known as NYU.
我更关心我的表哥来没来
I'm more concerned about my cousin.
他手里有我需要的东西
He has something I need.
肥皂 体香剂
Soap? Deodorant?
还是史上最牛香港脚药
The Toughest Actin' Tinactin?
他来了
Oh, there he is!
看来他没带体香剂
Well, he didn't bring the deodorant.
尤里 你总算来了
Yuri, you made it.
你是脱衣舞娘吗
Are you the stripper?
或许几年之后会是
Probably in a few years.
你把文件带来了吗
Did you bring the papers?
我要用来结婚的文件
The papers I need to get married?
还有我最爱的乌克兰小糖果
And those little Ukrainian candies I love?
坏消息
Bad news.
那个伪造文件的家伙被驱逐出境了
The guy who made the fake papers got deported.
文件被人带走了
They took the papers.
糖果被我吃掉了
I ate the candy.
我错过了什么
What'd I miss?
除了出人头地的机会之外
Besides my chance to become something?
你是脱衣舞娘吗
Are you the stripper?
不是[俄语]
Nyet.
一个词就恭维和羞辱齐发
A compliment and an insult in just one word.
不
Oh, no.
不 不 不 不
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
我刚说"不"了吗
Did I mention "No"?
你也好意思说这个字
How can you say the word "No"
女人说"不"的时候怎么就不懂啥意思呢
but not understand it when women say it?
这简直是一场灾难
This is a disaster.
而且还不是我可以趁火打劫的那种
And not the kind where I can loot.
我需要假文件来重新申请假绿卡
I needed those fake papers to renew my fake green card.
我的绿卡下个月就失效了
Mine expires next month.
你什么时候在乎失效期了
Since when do you care about expiration dates?
你做饭的鸡蛋都老到变战斗公鸡了
You cook with eggs so old they fight back.
苏菲绝不会相信我是因为一张绿卡
Sophie will never believe that I'm not marrying her
而不能跟她结婚
just for a green card.
她超不信任人
She has major trust issues
因为小时候某天 她父亲出去买波兰饺子
since one day, her father went out for pierogies and...
结果回家没带波兰饺子
came back without pierogies.
我真的很享受"齐逼骆驼趾"女子组合
I'm really enjoying the dance stylings
在上面搔首弄姿
of Camel and Toe up there.
大家都玩得很开心 除了奥列格
Everyone is having fun except Oleg.
我都没怎么看见他把手放到嘴上
I haven't seen him so much as put the "V" Fingers
冲着任何女人用手指比V
in front of his mouth at any of these ladies.
我不介意跟她隔着毛衣蹭蹭
Wouldn't mind some over the sweater action with her.
蹭她的还是蹭你的
Hers or yours?
麦克斯 我刚做了一件从未做过的事
Max, I just did something I've never done.
说不是自己的事吗
Told a story about someone else?
不 我刚给机长发了一张咪咪照
No, I sent the pilot a boob pic.
妹子 你个浪货
Girl, you nasty.
我知道 我超级浪
I know. I am nasty!
我看着镜头露出咪咪 然后按下发送键
I just looked into the camera with my boobs out and hit send.
呵呵 太棒了
Ah-ha, that's awesome.
现在回顾下步骤
Uh, circling back now,
你刚是说你看着镜头吗
did you say you looked into the camera?
你没有把你的脸拍进去 对吗
You didn't put your face in it, did you?
妹子
Girl!
你个蠢货
You stupid.
不然他怎么知道是我呢
How else would he know it was me?
咪咪照绝不能把自己的脸拍进去
You never put your face in it.
养女千日 毁于一照
Didn't I raise you better than this?
算了 至少你没笑眯眯的吧
Well, at least you weren't smiling in it.
真是败给你了 哪种笑
All right, what kind of smile?
轻浮的假笑勉强过关
A flirty smirk could work.
勾人的露齿笑更好
A come-hither grin would be great.
我的更像是...
More like...
所以你是以这个...
So you were in this...
姿势露出你的奶子
pose with your yabbos out?
裸体酸奶广告式的笑容呗
So you basically did a nude yogurt ad.
可是是那种你想"睡"的酸奶 对吧
Yeah, but like yogurt you want to have sex with, right?
完蛋了
Oh, my God.
苏菲随时会来
Sophie will be here any minute.
我刚才打给她 她在洗头发
When I called, she was washing her hair.
她把头发戴回头上后就会过来
She was going to put it back on her head and come.
你就实话实说吧
Just be honest with her.
虽然有时真相很丑陋
Sometimes the truth is ugly.
但她知道这一点 毕竟她见过你裸体了
But she knows that. She's seen you naked.
机长没回短信 你的丑事肯定没我这个丑
Well, still no text back so apparently not as ugly as this.
这是几个意思
What's that about?
你现在开始卖房地产了吗
Are you selling real estate now?
哇 瞧瞧
Oh, wow.
这个派对真是淫荡到不能再淫荡了
I mean, this party couldn't get any sleazier
除非你们把骚宾西克也请来
unless you invited Robin Thicke.
我抬头看见群婊乱舞
I'm looking up at skanky whore city,
但我相信你 奥列格
but I trust you, Oleg.
真的吗
You do?
真的呀 为什么不呢
Yeah, why wouldn't I?
暂且不谈我复杂的过去
Aside from my complicated past
以及骗过我的几卡车男人
full of men that have lied to me.
但我和你之间没有秘密 不是吗 奥列格
But you and I don't have secrets from each other, right, Oleg?
是的 我想说...
Yeah, well, you see--
下面进行传统环节"伴郎有话说"
It is time for the traditional best man speech.
所以都给我听好啦 小婊砸们
So listen up, bitches.
哎哟 好痛
Ow, damn it.
我流血了
I am bleeding.
再重复一次 我流血了
Repeat, I am bleeding.
真是气死人了
I can't believe this.
这世上有一摇手机就发出打嗝声的无聊应用
There's an app that burps when you shake your phone,
却没有撤销咪咪照的实用应用吗
but no app that unsends a boob pic?
苏菲 奥列格
Sophie. Oleg.
关于这两小家伙该说点什么好呢
What's there to say about these two kids?
奥列格是个烂厨子
Oleg is a bad cook.
苏菲说话超大声
Sophie, quite loud.
但当他们合而为一时 魔法发生了
But somehow, when they get together, magic.
烂透了 下一个
You suck, next act!
在机场工作的服务员还有脸说我烂
Says the lady that works at the airport.
奥列格 我很高兴苏菲跟你结婚
And, Oleg, I'm so glad Sophie is marrying you
这样你就可以留在美国了
so now you can stay in the country.
糟糕 呃...
Oh, no. Uh...
烂透了 下一个
You suck. Next act?
我也觉得 妹子
Yeah, I hear ya girl.
刚才那个笑话连笑点都没有
I mean that last joke didn't even have a punch line.
就是 感觉太可悲了
Yeah, I mean, it was sort of sad.
那不是笑话
It was no joke.
这是认真的
This is serious.
这真的很严重
It's really serious.
那张咪咪照现在已经传到云端了
That boob pic is up in the Cloud now.
各位 我的咪咪在云端
My boob is in the Cloud, y'all.
苏菲 我不知道该怎么告诉你
Sophie, I didn't know how to tell you.
你居然为了绿卡跟我结婚
You wanted to marry me for a green card?
我还以为你是为了我的肉体
See, I thought you were marrying me for my bod.
或是为了我在品牌家居店的关系 或...
Or for my connections at The Container Store, or...
我一手把你带大 还教会你识字啊
I mean, I taught you how to read!
苏菲 我可以解释
Sophie, I can explain.
不必了 婚礼取消
No, no, no. The wedding's off.
天啊
Oh, no.
那些被我刷成婚礼白的鸽子
What the hell am I going to do with all those pigeons
该怎么处置啊
that I had painted wedding white?
苏菲 别走
Sophie, wait.
瞧瞧谁出来了
Aww, well, look who it is.
我亲爱的要被驱逐出境男
My dearly deported.
我在来的路上想好的这段开场白
I worked on that the whole way over.
苏菲 我不会被驱逐出境
Sophie, I'm not gonna be deported.
我会随便找个人结婚 好留在美国
I'm gonna marry someone so I can stay in this country
把你追回来
and win you back.
我不在乎我的新娘是谁
I don't care who my new bride is.
先声明 不能是我
Just upfront, it can't be me.
因为众所周知 我已经把终生托付给工作了
'Cause everybody knows I'm married to my work.
也不能是我
And it can't be me.
反正就是不行
It just can't.
都不见得得是新娘 新郎也行嘛
They don't even have to be the best or even good.
标准什么都是浮云
Standards are out the window.
瞧 加州葡萄干的吉祥物来了
Look, it's a California Raisin.
墨镜加止痛片
Sunglasses and Advil.
昨晚的确超级疯狂啊
Last night was mad real.
阿憨
Han,
你愿意为了让我留在美国而跟我结婚吗
will you marry me so I can stay in the country?
我得考虑考虑
I'll need to think about it.
我愿意
Yes.
显然他唯一不愿意的事是给我们上医保
Apparently the only thing he won't say yes to is health care.
奥列格 我不相信你
Oleg, I don't believe you.
这不过又是你耍的小诡计
This is just another trick to get me to do
骗我做你想我做的事
what you want me to do.
就像上次你不断地把冰淇淋"掉"到你大腿间
Like when you kept "Dropping" your ice cream into your lap.
没有诡计
No trick.
有时爱会让你做出疯狂而恶心的事情
Sometimes love makes you do crazy, disgusting things.
像这样
Like this.
过来 阿憨
Come here, Han.
现在我也爱上这份工作了
And now I love this job, too!
还好他选的是阿憨
Thank God he picked Han.
苏菲 奥列格一定非常爱你
Wow, Sophie. Oleg must really love you.
这对他来说一定很难
That had to be hard for him.
依我所见 对阿憨来说也有点小难[硬]
And from what I can see, a little hard for Han, too.
在我们的婚礼上 口气清新剂得多喷一下
At our wedding, maybe two pumps of breath spray.
阿憨 你不能跟奥列格结婚
Han, you're not marrying Oleg.
因为奥列格要跟我结婚
'Cause Oleg's marrying me.
我现在相信你了
I believe you now.
因为你亲了阿憨
'Cause you kissed Han,
而亚洲小妹根本不是你的菜
and Asian girls aren't even your thing.
天啊 麦克 这是我的咪咪照
Oh my God, Max, it's my boob pic.
有人把它做成一张网络火图
Someone made it into a meme.
乳房X线照片的火图吗
A mammo meme?
40岁以前按理不需要照这个的呀
You're not supposed to need those 'til you're 40.
我下半辈子都要"夹"在我咪咪照下抬不起头
My boob pic is gonna be hanging over me for the rest of my life.
得了吧
Oh, come on,
你的咪咪连一根铅笔都"夹"不住
your boob couldn't hang over a pencil.